http://www.franklinmillsco.com/privacy.php

Franklin Mills Co.
Corporate Accounts
WE
SHIP TO:
Shopping
Cart  (0)
Library/Education     •
Business & Mfg.
Integrated Solutions
High-Density Mobile StorageStationary Shelving SystemsProfessional Filing SystemsCorporate Document FoldersPatient Charting SystemsHuman Resource FoldersPatent & Trademark FoldersMedical Staff Folders
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our Home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Franklin Mills Company web site. On some pages you can order products or make requests. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
· Name
· Address
· E-Mail Address
· Phone Number
· Credit/Debit Card Information
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You may create a Customer Account at Franklin Mills Company to save your order history, detailed invoices, order tracking, shipping addresses and contact information for future visits. Customers may opt-in to receive discount coupons, new product information or sign-up for our Newsletter. Information that you submit will not be used to contact you unless you request product updates and/or sign-up for our Newsletter. You may unsubscribe from our Newsletter at any time.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Home » Privacy Policy
Franklin
Mills Co. - Experience is the difference.
Toll free 1-888-678-4585
Franklin Mills Co.
· Business / Mfg.
Medical Filing Carts (HIPAA)
